<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Kokori News</title>
    <description>Kokori News</description>
    <link>http://kokori.grogue.org</link>
    <image>
      <title>Kokori News</title>
      <url>http://s.dsimg.com/image/A-1750478-1269556274.jpeg</url>
      <link>http://kokori.grogue.org</link>
    </image>
    <language>en-EN</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 00:44:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <item>
                <title>Kokori participates in Portuguese Industrial compilation</title>
                <description>
                  Kokori has participated in "Passo a Passo", a free Portuguese Industrial compilation from the Anti-Demos-Cracia label, with the track "The Sky Is Concrete, The Stars Are Bullet Holes", taken from our album "Rootkit". It was a pleasure to be included in such a compilation, featured alongside names like Nothing: Always: Works:, Waste Disposal Machine or Teatro Grotesco, amongst others. We could spill some lines about the compilation, but, instead, why don't you just &lt;a href="http://anti-demos-cracia.bandcamp.com/album/passo-a-passo-est-ticas-sonoras"&gt;stream or download&lt;/a&gt; it? Enjoy!
                </description>
                <link>https://anti-demos-cracia.bandcamp.com/track/kokori-the-sky-is-concrete-the-stars-are-bullet-holes</link>
                <pubDate>Sun, 08 May 2016 00:44:05 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
                <title>Kokori announces first full-length album: Rootkit</title>
                <description>
		  Kokori is very proud to announce that the moment you all have been waiting for has finally arriving. The revolution starts with the deployment of a rootkit, and Kokori's Rootkit is finally here. That's right, Kokori has signed a deal with Artapes, and the band's first full-length album, named Rootkit, is going to hit the shelves very soon -- Monday 18th 2016, to be more precise. And because we all know how waiting can be boring, we devised a time-travelling rootkit enabler: you can already pre-order your copy, which will warrant you an insta-download! According to Artapes, Rootkit is "a dense soundscape of bleak isolationism from a nearby post-apocalyptic world. Sonority-wise, [..] voice as ‘just yet another instrument,’ and lyrics – when present – come in various formats – from actual singing to the use of various samples and voice synthesis." About half of the 13 tracks in the album are instrumental. To the followers, you'll recognize some of the tracks from previous singles/EPs, but now introduced as several functions to serve a main() purpose. Are you ready to &lt;a href="http://artapes.co.uk/product/kokori-rootkit/"&gt;deploy the Rootkit&lt;/a&gt;, and let the world of Kokori take over?
                </description>
		<link>http://artapes.co.uk/product/kokori-rootkit/</link>
                <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2015 12:15:04 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
	<item>
                <title>The Prisioner is out</title>
                <description>
				Fruit of your interest, the Metaphysical Circuits campaign was quite worthy - thank you! That means that 400/100, an awesome 3 tapes compilation from the Metaphysical Circuits tape label, has now been released. This three-hour, 43 track triple cassette compilation is an epic, eclectic statement, spanning ambient excursions, techno textures, slick synths, cinematic guitars, song-craft, improvisation, wyrld jamz, and no-fi noise melodies. Alongside with musical projects like Palm Era, TAKAHIRO MUKAI, Vejgaard Ambient, Northville Tunnels, The Child of a Creek, Stephen Connolly, Strange Mountain, cryptic scenery, Geoff, Les Bicyclettes de Belize and more, kokori features there a new, exclusive track, called "The Prisioner". You can now &lt;a href="https://metaphysicalcircuits.bandcamp.com/track/the-prisioner"&gt;stream it&lt;/a&gt; or own it, a digital copy of the compilation is &lt;a href="https://metaphysicalcircuits.bandcamp.com/album/400-100"&gt;as cheap as a five dollar bill&lt;/a&gt;, and if you prefer the full physical, visual and tactile experience, the 101 copies three tapes limited edtion still gives you a download code, and has the attractive &lt;a href="http://www.abeardofsnails.com/metaphysicalcircuitsshop/"&gt;$15 price tag, worldwide shipping included&lt;/a&gt;. So, what are you waiting for?
                </description>
		<link>https://metaphysicalcircuits.bandcamp.com/track/the-prisioner</link>
                <pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 11:14:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
                <title>Metaphysical Circuits 3x tape compilation</title>
                <description>
				With your help, Kokori is going to be part of an awesome 3 tapes compilation. Metaphysical Circuits, a tape label from our good friend Christian of The Beard Of Snails Records (R.I.P.), is aiming to release "400/100", a three-hour, 43 track triple cassette compilation. An epic, eclectic statement, spanning ambient excursions, techno textures, slick synths, cinematic guitars, song-craft, improvisation, wyrld jamz, and no-fi noise melodies, this project has everything to be a must-have compilation, and we're proud to be a part of it with one new, exclusive track. Alongside with Kokori will be musical projects like Palm Era, TAKAHIRO MUKAI, Vejgaard Ambient, Northville Tunnels, The Child of a Creek, Stephen Connolly, Strange Mountain, cryptic scenery, Geoff, Les Bicyclettes de Belize and more. But why with your help? Well, because this endeavour needs you as much as you need it: your funding and pre-order will make it happen, and in the process you can even get some extra goodies. Find all about it on &lt;a href="https://www.indiegogo.com/projects/metaphysical-circuits-3x-tape-compilation"&gt;its campaign page&lt;/a&gt;!
                </description>
                <link>https://www.indiegogo.com/projects/metaphysical-circuits-3x-tape-compilation</link>
                <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 00:01:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
                <title>Desert Moon / First Egg</title>
                <description>
				The great and already missed The Beard Of Snails Records, the label that released Kokori's debut, has, like many good things, come to an end. But they decided not to do so in a quiet fashion, but instead with a couple of BANG!'s. The final release of this label was also the latest Kokori release, a limited edition 7 inches single, with Desert Moon on the A-side and First Egg in the B-side. Because unfortunately there are many great things that end, Kokori decided to choose two tracks for this release that were born in the womb of another great now-ended project you probably heard of, by now: The 20th. And this limited edition journey and quest through a Desert Moon to reach at the First Egg has already found its place among the record colections of an enlighted few: but fear not, for if this relic is indeed sold out, you can still experience what you've just missed: just listen to the music player on the right bar of our website. If you, like us, want to pay tribute to the life of this record label, that categorized this latest single as "Darker techwave sensibilities meet scorched Zappa cheese; the sonic importance of the vacuum cleaner; The Son of the Sheik meets Metropolis...?!", remember: the "Bearded Snails" compilation Kokori participated on is &lt;a href="http://abeardofsnails.storenvy.com/products/5204081-v-a-bearded-snails-3x-3"&gt;still on sale&lt;/a&gt;.
                </description>
                <link>http://abeardofsnails.bandcamp.com/album/desert-moon-first-egg</link>
                <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2014 16:22:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
		<item>
                <title>Kokori on Feedbands</title>
                <description>
				Feedbands is an experimental crowdsourced record company dedicated to spreading awesome tunes and supporting independent musicians. With Feedbands, you can listen to the music that artists submit to them, vote on your favorites, and see the highest-rated bands get their record pressed. Then, when you subscribe to Feedbands, they ship the record right to your door each month. Sounds exciting? We thought so, and joined the bandwagon (pun intended). So, you can now &lt;a href="https://feedbands.com/kokori"&gt;listen to Kokori on Feedbands&lt;/a&gt; and vote on our tracks - you might even help us release an LP by doing so! And, to make things even more interesting, one of the tracks we have there, "The Sky Is Concrete, The Stars Are Bullet Holes", is an exclusive, new track, you'll only be able to listen there!
                </description>
                <link>https://feedbands.com/kokori</link>
                <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2014 16:36:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
 
		<item>
                <title>Kokori on Feedbands</title>
                <description>
				Feedbands is an experimental crowdsourced record company dedicated to spreading awesome tunes and supporting independent musicians. With Feedbands, you can listen to the music that artists submit to them, vote on your favorites, and see the highest-rated bands get their record pressed. Then, when you subscribe to Feedbands, they ship the record right to your door each month. Sounds exciting? We thought so, and joined the bandwagon (pun intended). So, you can now &lt;a href="https://feedbands.com/kokori"&gt;listen to Kokori on Feedbands&lt;/a&gt; and vote on our tracks - you might even help us release an LP by doing so! And, to make things even more interesting, one of the tracks we have there, "The Sky Is Concrete, The Stars Are Bullet Holes", is an exclusive, new track, you'll only be able to listen there!
                </description>
                <link>https://feedbands.com/kokori</link>
                <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2014 15:41:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
                <title>Kokori on vinyl: Release Candid Hate</title>
                <description>
                Just released by &lt;a href="https://www.facebook.com/newapproachrecords"&gt;New Approach Records&lt;/a&gt;, kokori finally releases its new EP, "&lt;strong&gt;Release Candid Hate&lt;/strong&gt;". This is the harshest and yet the most beautiful kokori release to date. Following the minimalistic ambiences you've grown to love from &lt;strong&gt;make install&lt;/strong&gt;, the previous EP, Release Candid Hate joins it strong lyrics and instrumental voices. The EP, a vinyl release that comes with a digital download coupon for those of you who are afraid of needles, is available in its &lt;a href="http://newapproachrecords.tictail.com/product/kokori-release-candid-hate"&gt;standard edition&lt;/a&gt;, a 7 inches disc, or a more limited &lt;a href="http://newapproachrecords.wordpress.com/vinyl/"&gt;special edition&lt;/a&gt; of 20, that adds a transparent single-sided 5 inches vinyl to the pack.
                </description>
                <link>http://newapproachrecords.wordpress.com/vinyl/</link>
                <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2013 18:52:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
	<item>
		<title>New free() EP: make install</title>
		<description>
		Just released at &lt;a href="http://enoughrecords.scene.org/"&gt;Enough Records&lt;/a&gt;, kokori presents its new EP "make install". In the label's own words: "Portuguese industrial post-cyberpunk project kokori delivers us here an EP compiling a set of instrumental geek shaman electronic burlesque sounds with some sampling of local political activism." This EP, which you can &lt;a href="http://freemusicarchive.org/music/kokori/make_install/"&gt;listen or download for free&lt;/a&gt;, sums up an era, while installing the roots of great things to come.
		</description>
		<link>http://freemusicarchive.org/music/kokori/make_install/</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2013 10:27:19 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>New (free) track, "Timeless"</title>
		<description>
		Like last year, at the beginning of 2013 a new compilation arrived: Each month, on the 20th of the month, a bunch of people from all kinds of places start making songs. And then they finish them, that same day! Why would they do that? It doesn't matter! The songs are great! Very often! Kokori also participated, and you can listen or download (free!) the &lt;a href="http://the20th.bandcamp.com/track/timeless"&gt;Timeless&lt;/a&gt; result!
		</description>
		<link>http://the20th.bandcamp.com/track/timeless</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2013 14:47:11 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>New track on Bearded Snails</title>
		<description>
		To celebrate its 100th release, A Beard Of Snails Records (the label that released kokori's first EP, init()), decided to release a 3CD 
		compilation, that includes a fresh new Kokori track, "Attention". So, what are you waiting for? &lt;a href="http://abeardofsnails.com/shop.html"&gt;grab it!&lt;/a&gt;
		</description>
		<link>http://abeardofsnails.com/shop.html</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 09:11:11 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>

	<item>
		<title>2012, so far</title>
		<description>
		We've haven't been signaling radio noise, but some things transpired.&lt;br/&gt; 
		We released &lt;a href="http://daidalosrec.bandcamp.com/track/inbrase"&gt;Inbrase&lt;/a&gt; on a compilation,
		&lt;a href="http://the20th.bandcamp.com/track/apert"&gt;Apert&lt;/a&gt; on another.&lt;br/&gt;
		&lt;a href="http://soundcloud.com/kokoript/pl118"&gt;#PL118&lt;/a&gt; got our attention, 
		and our attention got &lt;a href="http://www.mixcloud.com/enoughrecords/99-anonymous-mixtape-4/"&gt;Anonymous attention&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;
		Last but not least, we've created a &lt;a href="https://kokori.grogue.org/mailman/listinfo/friends"&gt;list for Kokori friends&lt;/a&gt;, so why don't you join?
		</description>
		<link>http://kokori.grogue.org</link>
		<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jun 2012 01:11:11 GMT</pubDate>
	</item>
    <item>
      <title> Necktar 2017 volume 3 </title>
      <description>
Necktar 2017 is a compilation
of hors norme (not normal) music for free sharing,
articulated in several thematic episodes and cycles.
Kokori just participated in the third volume of this compilation, which is centered around the theme &quot;Macro / Perception / Micro : Evolution&quot;. Grab the physical release of this compilation &lt;a href="http://www.discogs.com/buy/DVDr/Various-Necktar-2017-Volume-3/35506181?ev=bp_det"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.
</description>
      <link>http://www.discogs.com/buy/DVDr/Various-Necktar-2017-Volume-3/35506181?ev=bp_det</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 02:09:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>That's What I Call Retro-Futurism</title>
        <description>
At October 2010, the compilation "NOW 1 - That's What I Call Retro-Futurism" was released.
14 bands on two recycled floppy disks in a plastic case, to celebrate the DER's 10th release. All tracks in under 150K. Includes new tracks from Merankorii, kokori (a new track) and others. Limited to 35 copies, this is sold-out.
        </description>
        <link>http://disketteetikette.bigcartel.com/about-us</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2010 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Free compilation &quot;Basic Imprint&quot;</title>
      <description>&lt;a href="http://www.archive.org/details/V.a.BasicImprintkopp.13"&gt;Basic Imprint&lt;/a&gt; is a 2CD free netlabel compilation of dark and experimental cinematic music, by Kopp Netlabel.

Includes tracks by &lt;a href="http://www.reverbnation.com/merankorii"&gt;Merankorii&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;Kokori&lt;/strong&gt; (Terror Attack, a new track from us, which might be available in the future with better sound) and others. It's a free download, so what are you waiting for?
</description>
      <link>http://www.archive.org/details/V.a.BasicImprintkopp.13</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 06:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kokori debut EP, &quot;init( )&quot; is OUT ! </title>
      <description>Kokori's debut CDr has been released through A Beard of Snails Records, an independent publisher. The sales pitch: "Far-reaching, rhythmic darkwave-y fairytale ambient machine (sometimes pop) music from Portuguese powerhouses +ko+ko+ and Merankorii. The most (goth?) club-destined A Beard of Snails release to date?! Limited edition of 16."
This is now sold out. Click &lt;a href="http://www.discogs.com/Kokori-init/release/2320019"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to know more about it.
</description>
      <link>http://www.myspace.com//kokoript/blog/535910217</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2010 07:48:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
